Let's talk about where the broker houses are
looking. Our colleague Vamakshi is telling
us about the power sector. There is a
report from the government sector. They have
said for Tata Power that medium term
gains are visible. There is
also limited growth potential. Due to this,
they have started coverage
with a target price of 190%.
Apart from this, they say that the exponential
growth can
also get a boost because they have
commissioned two big plants. So
due to this, the
price may be 55%.
On NTPC, they say that it will
emerge as a winner in the transition. The
company has a low cost advantage and in
fact, a rising stock, due to which their
legacy thermal business has relative strength.
Due to this, they have started coverage on NTPC
with a target price of 265. Apart from this,
on the running balance, we are seeing that
IndusInd Bank is on the watch. We are seeing
reports from many broker houses, Kotak and  Govt. Sachs has
maintained its buy rating.
Mohan Saini has maintained his overweight rating
and GP Morgan has maintained a neutral
rating. However, all the stock
houses have raised their target prices.
Progress is larger. It says that
margins have been stable in Q1. Growth outlook
appears to be improving and in fact,
credit costs are also seen to be falling.
If the founders increase their stake
in the bank, it could be a positive and
due to this, we are looking at it. Apart from this, ICC
Lombard says that the
company has
posted growth which is very strong, better than the industry growth. Combined ratios have
posted improvement here
and in fact, growth momentum is
looking very strong in the health and commercial segments, hence,
Oval has
given this rating. They say that the
company has given very strong results in the first quarter. Very
strong execution has been seen and
a good play is seen on the Indian infrastructure and housing sectors, due to which a
buy rating has been given by them.  And due to
this fact, they have increased their target price
to 48% and finally we
will focus on Havells, remember yesterday we saw
that UPS had started recovery and today
Motilal Oswal has started recovery and has
given a target price of
1580% with a buy opinion, they say that there is a very
diversified portfolio, the market is changing
and in this segment,
which company is trying to increase the distribution channel
and by strengthening the in-house manufacturing, the
earnings and return ratio
can also improve, so due to this, we are
seeing that Motilal Oswal has
started coverage with a buyer opinion on Havells to
give all this information.